Ferargil Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Business and Financial Records, 1919-1956, Series 4:; (Boxes 18-21; 1.2 linear ft.)
  - Invoices and Receipts for Artwork, 1919-1920, 1927-1944, (8 folders) (Box 19, Folder 7-24)
  - Invoices and Receipts for Artwork, 1945-1956, (5 folders) (Box 20, Folder 1-5)
  - Lists, Artwork Sold, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Lists, Miscellaneous, circa 1920s-1950s, (2 folders) (Box 20, Folder 7-8)
  - Notes and Memoranda, circa 1920s-circa 1950s, (2 folders) (Box 20, Folder 9-10)
  - Presidents Reports, 1938, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Shipping Records, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Statements of Accounts, circa 1920s-circa 1950s (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Statements of Accounts, 1925-1942, (3 folders) (Box 20, Folder 14-16)
  - Statements of Accounts, 1943-1956, (4 folders) (Box 21, Folder 1-4)
  - Tax Records, 1930s-1950s (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Trip Reports, 1932-1933 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Printed Material, circa 1900-1956, Series 5:; (Boxes 21-22; 0.7 linear ft.)
  Printed material consists primarily of catalogs for exhibitions at Ferargil Galleries and scattered announcement cards. Other printed material is also generally art-related, and includes material from other galleries, art institutions, and companies such as exhibition catalogs and reviews, as well as a folder of printed material relating to Arthur B. Davies (including an article by Royal Cortissoz and a Davies obituary) and a folder of press releases and other miscellanous information regarding exhibitions.
  - Ferargil Galleries (Box 21)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, circa 1920s-circa 1950s (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1918-1930s, (5 folders) (Box 21, Folder 8-12)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1940s, (1-3 of 6 folders) (Box 21, Folder 13-15)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1940s, (4-6 of 6 folders) (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1950s (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - News Clippings, 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Other, circa 1900-1956, (6 folders) (Box 22, Folder 6-11)
  - Other, Arthur B. Davies, 1905, 1929-1943 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Other, Exhibitions, 1930s-1940s (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Scrapbooks, circa 1920s-1950s, Series 6:; (Boxes 23-34, 40, OV 41; 5.4 linear ft.)
  Scrapbooks include printed material and photographs. Printed matter primarily consists of news clippings in addition to exhibition catalogs (some annotated with prices), scattered correspondence, and other gallery documentation such as artist biographical material, press releases, exhibition lists, and exhibition guest signature lists. Photographs are primarily of artwork, with scattered photos of artists and exhibitions, including a photograph of Arthur B. Davies taken by Gertrude Kasëbier, circa 1908.
  Correspondence found with scrapbooks includes a 1929 letter from Royal Cortissoz to Price expressing his opinion on the first part of Price's biography of Arthur B. Davies, a copy of which is attached to the letter. Also found is a 1952 letter from Boris Lovet-Lorski describing an accident involving a bronze sculpture that fell on him in his studio.
  An attempt has been made to establish the original collation of the scrapbooks. There appears to have been one general scrapbook arranged by artist (which is incomplete), a group of smaller scrapbooks devoted to individual artists, a scrapbook for sculptors, and a scrapbook for paintings and other media (also incomplete entitled "Painting Publicity.") Found also is one exhibition scrapbook for the "New Collectors Exhibition" in 1940. Most of the photographs were removed from the scrapbooks during previous processing and are housed separately at the end of the series.
  Within scrapbooks material is generally arranged alphabetically by artist. Various fragments, which were presumably housed in the general scrapbook, can be found at the end of the series.
  - Scrapbook Arranged by Artist (Box 23)
    - A-D, F, circa 1920s-1950s, (5 folders) (Box 23, Folder 1-5)
    - L, M, S, circa 1920s-1950s, (6 folders) (Box 24, Folder 1-6)
  - Individual Artist Scrapbooks (Box 25)
    - Bostelle, Tom, circa 1920s-1950s, (2 folders) (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
    - Cantine, Jo, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Carter, Clarence, circa 1920s-1950s, (3 folders) (Box 25, Folder 4-6)
    - Cheney, Russell, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Collette, Maurice, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Cotton, Lillian, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Cowles, Russell, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Crimi, Alfred D., circa 1920s-1950s (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Dyer, Nancy, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Davies, Arthur B., circa 1920s-1950s, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Davies, Arthur B., circa 1920s-1950s, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - George, Thomas, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Gregory, Waylande, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Groth, John, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Heuston, George, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Hoyt, Edith, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Hudson, Eric, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Jones, Amy, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Munsell, Richard, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Painting Publicity Scrapbooks (Box 28)
    - E-L, circa 1920s-1950s, (4 folders) (Box 28, Folder 1-4)
    - M-T, circa 1920s-1950s, (4 folders) (Box 29, Folder 1-4)
    - V-Z, Miscellaneous, circa 1920s-1950s, (2 folders) (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
  - Sculpture Publicity Scrapbooks, A-Y, circa 1920s-1950s, (4 folders) (Box 30, Folder 3-6)
  - Sculpture Publicity, Kalcreuth, Baroness Von, Photos by Harold Stein, circa 1930s (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Exhibition Scrapbook, New Collectors Exhibition, Summer Show, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook Fragments, circa 1920s-1950s, (7 folders) (Box 31, Folder 2-8)
  - Correspondence found with Scrapbooks, 1929-1952 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Printed Material found with Scrapbooks, circa 1930s-1950s (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Guest Signature List found with Scrapbooks, circa 1940s (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Photographs from scrapbooks for (Box 32)
    - Abell, Margaret, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Anderson, C. W., circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Bemelmans, Ludwig, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 3)
      (includes photo of Bemelmans)
    - Buller, Audrey, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Parsons, Lloydcirca 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 5)
      (includes photo of Parsons)
    - Cantine, Jocirca 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Carter, Clarence, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Cheney, Russell, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Collette, Maurice, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 9)
      (includes photos of Collette)
    - Constant, George, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Cotton, Lillian, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Cowles, Russell, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Crespi, Pachita, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 13)
      (2 photos of Crespi)
    - Crimi, Alfred D., circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Davies, Arthur B., circa 1920s-1950s, (12 folders; oversized material housed in Box 40, OV 41) (Box 32, Folder 15-26)
      (includes circa 1908 photograph of Davies by Gertrude Kasëbier)
    - Dodd, Lamar, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 27)
      (includes photo of Dodd)
    - Dyer, Nancy, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Eilshemius, Louis, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - English School, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Ford, Lauren, circa 1920s-1950s, (4 folders) (Box 32, Folder 31-34)
    - Fenerley, John, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Foshko, Josef, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Franciabigio, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - George, Thomas, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 38)
      (includes photo of George)
    - Gheerardts, Marc the Younger, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Gregory, Waylande, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 40)
      (includes 2 photos of Gregory)
    - Groth, John, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Hare, Channing, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Hesketh, circa 1920s-1950s, (4 folders) (Box 32, Folder 43-46)
      (includes photos of Hesketh, studio and Ferargil Galleries storefront displaying Hesketh work)
    - Heuston, George F., circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 47)
      (includes photo of Heuston and photo of Heuston and others in Egypt, 1942)
    - Holbein Studio, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - Howard, Wing, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Hoyt, Edith, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Hudson, Eric, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 33, Folder 3)
      (includes photo of Hudson)
    - Jones, Amy, circa 1920s-1950s, (4 folders) (Box 33, Folder 4-7)
    - King, Clinton, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 33, Folder 8)
      (includes 4 photos of King)
    - Lavalle, John, circa 1920s-1950s, (3 folders) (Box 33, Folder 9-11)
    - Lee, R. J., circa 1920s-1950s (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Lely, Sir Peter, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Lovet-Lorski, Boris, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 33, Folder 14)
      (includes 5 photos of Lovet-Lorski)
    - Lowrie, Agnes Potter, circa 1920s-1950s, (2 folders) (Box 33, Folder 15-16)
    - Lucioni, Luigi, circa 1920s-1950s, (5 folders; oversized material housed in OV 41) (Box 33, Folder 17-21)
    - Luttichuijs, Simon, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Margules, De Hirsch, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Mays, Maxwell, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - McCouch, Gordon, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Miller, Barse, circa 1920s-1950s, (2 folders) (Box 33, Folder 26-27)
    - Morani, Gianbattista, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Munsell, Richard, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 33, Folder 29)
      (includes photo of Munsell)
    - Paradise, Phil, circa 1920s-1950s, (2 folders) (Box 33, Folder 30-31)
      (includes photo of Paradise)
    - Parrish, Maxfield, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Robins, Louisa, circa 1920s-1950s, (2 folders) (Box 33, Folder 33-34)
    - Romney, George, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Ryder, Albert Pinkham, circa 1920s-1950s, (5 folders; oversized material housed in OV 41) (Box 33, Folder 36-40)
    - Salviati, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Sample, Paul, circa 1920s-1950s, (3 folders) (Box 33, Folder 42-44)
      (includes photo of Sample)
    - Sculpture Scrapbook, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Shattuck, Ross, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Shinn, Everett, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Sternberg, Charlotte J., circa 1920s-1950s, (includes photos of Sternberg) (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Stretes, Gullim, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Van Dyck, Sir Anthony, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Wheelock, Warren, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 34, Folder 7)
      (includes photo of Wheelock)
    - Williams, Lois, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 34, Folder 8)
      (includes photo of Williams)
    - Wouverman, Philip, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Davies, Arthur B., Oversized Matted and Conserved Photograph by Getrude Kasëbier, circa 1920s-1950s, (see also Box 32 Folder 15) (Box 40)
  - Oversized Photographs of Artwork from Scrapbooks for Davies, Lucioni and Ryder, circa 1920s-1950s, (see also Box 32 F15, Box 33 F17, Box 33 F36) (Box OV 41)
- Frederic Newlin Price Records, 1920s-1950s, Series 7:; (Box 34; 6 folders)
  This series documents Price's involvement with the Benjamin West Society at Swarthmore College and also contains an inventory of Price's art collection, and drafts, typescripts and published copies of some of Price's writings, including a biography of Arthur B. Davies.
  - Benjamin West Society of Swarthmore College, circa 1930s-1940s, (3 folders) (Box 34, Folder 10-12)
  - Inventory of Price Collection, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Price Writings, Drafts and Typescripts, circa 1930s-1950s (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Price Writings, Published Articles and Catalogs, 1920s-1940s (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Artwork, circa 1920s-circa 1950s, Series 8:; (Box 34; 2 folders)
  This series consists of 6 pencil sketches, 1 print, and 3 plans, all by unidentified artists. Also found is a mock-up of an exhibition catalog of Arthur B. Davies sculpture and carvings with pencil sketches by an unidentified artist and price notes for each entry.
  - Pencil Sketches, Print, and Plans, circa 1920s-circa 1950s, (oversized material housed in OV 41) (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Arthur B. Davies Exhibition Catalog Mock-Up, circa 1920s-circa 1930s (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Oversized Plans, circa 1920s-circa 1950s, (oversized material from Box 34 F16) (Box OV 41)
- Photographs, circa 1920-1950s, Series 9:; (Boxes 35-39, OV 40; 4.4 linear ft.)
  The series consists of the galleries photograph files containing primarily photographs of works of art, in addition to a few photographs of artists and of exhibitions and collections.
  Photographs are arranged alphabetically within 3 categories: artists, exhibitions and collections, and artwork.
  - Photographs of Artists (Box 35)
    - Carlsen, Emil, circa 1910, (oversized material housed in OV 40) (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Dabo, Leon, circa 1940s (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Davidson, Jo, circa 1930s (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Hesketh, circa 1940s (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Lux, Theodore, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Oenslager, Donald, circa 1949 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Parsons, Lloyd, circa 1940s (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Van Vleck, Natalie, circa 1940s (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Williams, Lois, circa 1940s (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Unidentified Individuals, circa 1920s-1930s (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Photographs of Exhibitions/Collections (Box 35)
    - "American Primitives," circa 1930s-1940s (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - "Art for the Home Front," circa 1945 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Averell House, circa 1930s-1940s, (2 folders) (Box 35, Folder 13-14)
    - "Circus Comes to Ferargil Galleries," circa 1940s (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Dan Fellows Platt Collection, circa 1930s-1940s (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Frick Library Photographs, circa 1930s-1940s (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Garden Furniture, circa 1930s-1940s (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Miniatures, circa 1930s-1940s (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Society Guido Minerbi & Co., circa 1930s-1940s (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - United China Relief, circa 1942 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Wrought Iron, circa 1930s-1940s, (2 folders) (Box 35, Folder 22-23)
  - Photographs of Artwork, By Artist (Box 35)
    - A: Ackley - Ashe, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - B: Babbott - Benton, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - B: Bertovici - Brush, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - B: Buller - Bull-Teilman, circa 1920s-1950s, (2 folders) (Box 35, Folder 27-28)
    - C: Campbell - Carson, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - C: Carter, Clarence, circa 1920s-1950s, (2 folders) (Box 35, Folder 30-31)
    - C: Cassatt - Chase, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - C: Cheney, Russell, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - C: Chi - Crespi, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - C: Crowell - Crowninshield, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - D: Dabo - Davey, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - D: Davies, Arthur B., circa 1920s-1950s, (11 folders) (Box 36, Folder 1-11)
    - D: Davis - Demitrios, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - D: Diedrich, Hunt, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - D: Dike, Phil, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - D: Dodd - Dyer, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - E: Eakins-Eggleson, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - F: Fabre, Madeleine, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - F: Faggi, Alfeo, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - F: Ferguson - Flagg, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - F: Folinsbee, John, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - F: Francis - Fuller, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - G: Gainsborough - Gill, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - G: Golinkin - Gramatky, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - G: Groll - Guy, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - H: Hale - Hassam, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - H: Hawthorne - Henri, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - H: Hesketh, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - H: Heuston - Hills, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - H: Homer - Houdon, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - H: Howard, Wing, circa 1920s-1950s, (2 folders) (Box 36, Folder 30-31)
    - H-I: Hoyt - Iacurto, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - I-K: Igarta - Kimball, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - K: Kingsbury, Alison Mason, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - K: Klauck - Korbel, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - L: Lafugie - Lane, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - L: Lane, Harry, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - L: Lathrop, William L., circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - L: Laukes - Lawrie, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - L: Lear - Lechay, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - L: Leith-Ross - Lucioni, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - L: Luks - Lux, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - M: Mabuse - Marsh, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - M: Martin - Mays, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - M: McCartan - McDonald, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - M: Menkes - Mills, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - M: Mintz - Mommer, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - M-N: Moose - Nordgren, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - O: O'Dea - Olson, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - P: Paisone - Paradise, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - P: Paro, Eugene, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - P: Parsons, Lloyd, circa 1920s-1950s, (2 folders) (Box 37, Folder 21-22)
    - P: Parrish - Pennoyer, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - P: Poole, Abram, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - P: Poupelet - Price, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - P: Purdy, Robert, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - R: Ranger - Remington, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - R: Richards - Rodin, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - R: Ross - Ryther, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - S: Saint-Gaudens - Sample, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - S: Sargent - Schwartz, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - S: Scott - Shrady, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - S: Skou - Stalter, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - S: Sternberg - Stuart, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - S-T: Sully - Thorne, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - T-V: Tolegia - Vanderlyn, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - V: van Marcke - van Soelen, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - V: Van Vleck, Natalie, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - V-W: Veib - Walds, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - W: Walker, Horatio, circa 1920s-1950s, (2 folders) (Box 38, Folder 15-16)
    - W: Waltman - Weston, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - W: Wheeler - Whistler, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - W: Whitaker, Frederic, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - W: Whittredge - Williams, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - W: Wilson - Wyeth, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Y: Yarrow - Yeats, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Artists, Unidentified and Miscellaneous, circa 1920s-1950s, (5 folders) (Box 38, Folder 23-27)
    - Artists, D, S: Negatives of artwork by Arthur B. Davies and Paul Sample, circa 1920s-1950s, (damaged) (Box 39)
    - Carlsen, Emil, circa 1910, (see also Box 35 F1) (Box 40, Folder 1)